Mary Hee

CONTACT

2

Kuala Lumpui





SKILLS

- Data analytics
- Sales and marketing strategy
- Client communication
- Person-centred practise
- Contract and deal negotiation
- Commitment to excellence
- Deadline management

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Built and nurtured key client relationships to grow profit by 130% YoY
- Enhanced processes, implementing across department for increased productivity and profits.
- Improved shippers reviews by successfully handling customer complaints and implementing monthly staff training.

I am experienced working in fast-paced environments demanding strong organizational and interpersonal skills. Highly motivated, ethical, and committed to superior customer service level. Confident and poised in interactions with individual at all levels. Detail-oriented and resourceful in completing projects and able to multi-task effectively. Possessing enthusiasm as a team player and experienced in leading and managing a business team.

EXPERIENCE

April 2021 - Current

Customer Success Management Lead Changee Sdn Bhd

- Liaised with stakeholders to identify key sales objectives and devise strategies to achieve goals.
- Identified market gaps for new and updated products and services.
- Advised business clients on best mix of products for maximum sales and consumer engagement.
- Monitored consumer patterns, anticipating changes and maintaining marketing strategy relevance in dynamic landscape.
- Developed research strategies to assess market demand for new offerings.
- Analysed market trends and demand to develop accurate pricing strategies.
- Responsible for team management, as well as acting as daily point of escalation for queries.
- Exceeded specific team goals and resolved issues, partnering with upper management team to share and implement continuous improvements.

September 2018 - March 2021

Business Development Manager Awesome-Car Sdn Bhd.

- Build and lead a team of business development executives and telemarketers
- Build strong relationship with new and existing clients as well as business partners
- Manage the portfolios of clients and keep them updated with new progress on a monthly basis
- Responsible for the monthly sales growth
- Meet monthly sales target and revenue
- Manage and coach the business development executives and telemarketers on a weekly basis
- Responsible for monthly team performance report.

June 2017 - August 2018

Senior Executive/Team Lead XYZ Sdn Bhd.

- Responsible for handling complains and escalations in the team
- Handle inbound calls and emails from corporate customers
- To establish an excellent rapport with potential customers and existing customers
- To train and supervise the team in handling complains and customer service skills
- Coach and manage six Customer Service Executive in the team
- Responsible for monthly team performance report

• In charge of Customer Loyalty Programme.

January 2015 - May 2017

Client Relationship Manager Plantation Berhad

- Build strong customer relationship with new and existing clients and create mutual trust
- Provide advice on financial solution based on identified needs
- Market and sell investment product to new and existing clients
- Manage and keep the portfolio of client updated with the company's progress and achievement
- Ensure credibility with clients by maintaining detailed knowledge of current market conditions and competitors' products
- Make cold calls to potential clients.

June 2013 - December 2014

Customer Care Professional ABCD (M) Sdn. Bhd

- Inbound Call Centre role answering calls from Hong Kong corporate clients
- Deliver exceptional customer service to every corporate cardholder
- Actively listen to all the card members' queries and problems, and proactively offer solutions and assistance.

EDUCATION

01/2012

(DIPLOMA) PROFESSIONAL INSTITUTE KUALA LUMPUR